翻译：Microsoft信仰中心 审核：imbushuo 压制：Microsoft信仰中心
So in my music collection
我的音乐收藏里
I literally have...
真的有
hundreds, hundreds of albums
很多很多专辑
that I've purchased legitimately through the years.
这些年，我在歌曲购买上可没少下功夫
And sometimes I don't even remember what I have,
有的专辑现在回过头来看，我都不记得我曾经买过
so I can concocted a little game here
所以在这里我可以做一些”特技“
that will allow you to rediscover music that you have
这些特技能让你重新发现你的专辑
in your music collection, in your music library,
在你的音乐歌单，在你的音乐库里
and will make a little game out of it.
下面开始进行游戏
And so you've gotta kind of watch closely here
你必须集中精力
at the game itself.
进行游戏
Alright, so these are songs, or album covers
好了，这个里面有许多歌曲和专辑封面
representing songs on my hard drive.
代表我的硬盘里的歌曲
(music plays)
（歌声响起）
Ok. And I successfully guessed that song
我成功猜出了这是哪首歌曲
and I got it right, and I scored 70 points
我猜对了，得了70 分
as a result of that.
是的，我得分了
Here we go, the next one.
那我进行下一首歌
(music plays)
（歌声响起）
Ok, I missed that one and I lost 80 points,
我猜测了，减80分
so I'm at a negative 10 after two rounds,
两轮过后，我的成绩是负 10 分
as you can see.
正如你所看到的那样
(music plays)
（歌声响起）
Alright, and so as you might guess,
你可能会猜到
this is not my music collection.
这不是并不在我的歌曲收藏里
I'll explain that in the next video,
这个我们在下个视频中进行解释
but these are purely songs that somebody
也有一些歌曲
created for me.
是某人为我创作的
(music plays)
（歌声响起）
But you can also see here that there's
你可以在下面
a little blue area down here.\看见一小块蓝色区域
This actually represents an advertisement
那个其实代表了
from Microsoft Advertisement Network.
一块来自微软广告网络的广告
(music plays)
（歌声响起）
Okay.
可以了
So you can see that after five rounds,
我们经过了五轮猜歌游戏后
I've got a massive negative score of 260.
我的成绩是负 260 分
I can choose to play again,
我可以选择重玩
but that's really not the most significant thing about this application
这并不是这个程序最重要的部分
What it will do is it'll allow you to go through
我们实际上做的是让你通过检查
special folders on the user's device
用户的磁盘
or desktop, specifically the music library.
桌面以及音乐库
And it'll go through every single folder
遍历每个其中文件夹
in the music library
在音乐库里
and find a list of all MP3 files.
找出所有 MP3 文件
It'll then grab the metadata from the MP3 file itself,
这个程序会抓取 MP3 文件的元数据
so information like the album name, the artist's name,
比如专辑名，艺术家名
the album art,
专辑封面
so you can see that we've got the cover art
所以，你可以看到我们已经挖掘出了
for the album itself,
专辑的封面
and then it's going to choose to randomly play songs
之后，程序会随机播放音乐
and as the user, I then have to guess,
这时候，你得猜
and it's going to evaluate my guess whether right or wrong
之后程序会对你的猜测进行评估（对/错）
and it will change the tile
之后程序会改变磁贴
as a result of that
作为结果
and it'll keep score, and there's a lot of logic
上面会呈现得分，这其中涉及了很多逻辑算法
around what songs to play,
哪些歌曲播放了
what to stay away from because you've already guessed
程序会排除你猜过歌曲
that album art or it's already been used once,
那些专辑封面
you can't use it because it's already got an X on it,
你将不能使那些被用过的歌曲封面
sort of thing, okay?
就是这样，你明白了吗？
Like I said, we demonstrate how to use
就像我说的那样，我们来演示一下吧
and monetize this application through Microsoft Advertising.
并且可以通过广告获利
We'll demonstrate that and then we'll also demonstrate
下面一起进行演示吧，同时
how to remove ads,
还会演示如何移除广告
so to add a premium feature to the app
通过增加高级付费功能
and allow you to monetize it
也可以让你从中获益
by allowing the user to click a button
只需要引导用户点击付费按钮
and it'll pop up the
接着跳出提示
"are you sure you want to purchase this for a dollar?"
“你愿意花费 1 美元来购买吗？”
Now, this is a little simulator and we'll talk about this
这只是一个简单的模拟
near the end of our time together building this,
在我们这节课接近尾声的时候，一起创建吧
but I'm going to go ahead and say "Yes,"
我们打算继续，并选择”好“
the user successfully purchased the removal of ads
就这样，用户成功购买了高级功能（去除了广告）
in the app.\这个应用程序就再也没有广告了
And so we're going to demonstrate how to add
接下来我们需要接着研究
in-app purchases in your application.
应用程序的内购
So there's a lot to learn in this app,
相信你们从这个例子里学了很多
it's going to be a lot of fun, a lot of logic,
你们应该会学的很开心，学到很多逻辑思维
a lot of typing,
输入了很多代码
so you'll need to follow along closely or you'll probably,
如果你想要更进一步，我想你们应该
honestly you'll probably just want to look at the source code
很想查看源代码
after I finish the video,
在这个视频结束后
but just follow along with the thought process
请紧跟这个程序的开发思维
as I work my way through this example.
通过这个案例，跟着我的思维走
Alright, ready?
准备好了吗？
Let's get started in the next video.
我们下期节目见
Thanks.
谢谢。